tadashishoji.com 2019-02-18

# Privacy Policy | Tadashi Shoji

Tadashi Shoji & Associates, Inc. and its websites (“we”, “our” or “us”) believe that your privacy is very important. This Policy outlines the types of personally identifiable or personal information and data that we will collect from you through the website at tadashishoji.com and its associated domain names (“Website”), and how we will use and when we might disclose such information and data to third parties. Your use of this Website and submission of information to us constitutes your consent to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 1, 2012 and was last modified on November 9, 2012.

 **Personal Information and Usage Data that we collect**

If you choose to open an account with our Website, we may collect your name, email address, physical address, date of birth, phone number, and/or fax number. If you choose to make a purchase through our Website, we will also collect your credit card information. The foregoing information is referred to herein collectively as your “Personal Information.” We will not collect any Personal Information from you simply by virtue of your visiting our Website; we only collect it if you choose to submit it to us. You represent and warrant that all Personal Information you provide us is true and correct and relates to you and not to any other person.

We also may collect standard usage information by virtue of your visiting the Website (“Usage Data”), such as your computer’s IP address, date and time of your visit to our Website, the type of browser you use, the URLs you visited before landing on the Website and to which you went afterwards, and other usage information, whether or not you submit Personal Information to us. Usage Data will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally.

Our servers, which may be hosted by one or more third parties, will store your Personal Information and may record your Usage Data.

 **Use of the Personal Information and Usage Data that we collect**

We may use your Personal Information to help us learn more about your shopping preferences and to enhance your shopping experience. We may also use your Personal Information in order to contact you to promote our Website and any specials we may offer. In the event that we send you advertising or marketing materials, we will provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such materials in the future. You may also opt-out of receiving such materials at any time in accordance with the instructions provided in this Privacy Policy

Usage Data may be used by us for administrative, analytical, research, optimization and other purposes, and this data in aggregated, anonymous form may be shared with third parties who provide such analytical, search and other optimization services.

In connection with the foregoing, we may also use cookies (tiny text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain web pages that identify your computer and may store information about you) and other technologies to learn more about your preferences on our Website, so that we can improve our services and our Website. From this we may learn what web pages you visit and how long various Website features are used (if any). The foregoing Usage Data and cookies will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally.

 **Disclosure of the Personal Information and Usage Data that we collect**

We will not sell, rent or transfer your Personal Information, except as otherwise indicated herein. We will not store your credit card information. In order to process credit card payments, we will use the service of a secure, third party credit card processor.

We use the services of third parties who will have limited access to your Personal Information to be used for specific purposes. These purposes may include credit card processing, order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, customer service, and data analysis. The third parties we contract with for these purposes will be authorized to use your Personal Information only for the purposes for which the party was engaged.

We may disclose your Personal Information or other information collected if required by law or court order, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, to investigate and/or take action against illegal activity, suspected abuse or unauthorized use of the Website, or to protect the property or safety of others.

In connection with any sale of our company or any line of business (including the assets relating thereto), customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and such customer information (including your Personal Information) will be transferred or sold to the acquirer in the event of any such sale or disposition of any or all of our business.

 **Credit Card Transactions**

If you choose to purchase a product from our Website, you represent and warrant that all credit card information you provide will be accurate and correct and that you are authorized to use such credit card. In no event will you provide us with any false or fraudulent information.

 **Your Rights**

We ask that you keep the Personal Information that you provide to us current and that you correct any information you have provided us by contacting us at [insert contact e-mail address].

If you wish to opt out of further communications from us, or if you wish to review, delete and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with your specific request at [customercare@tadashishoji.com](mailto:%20customercare@tadashishoji.com) provided, however, that we reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data and we further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such information.

You can decline to permit cookies in your browser, but in that case we cannot promise you that all Website features will function properly as a result.

If you use the Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account.

 **Partnerships and External Sources**

Our Website may link to external sites beyond our control. This privacy policy covers only the way we treat the Personal Information and Usage Data we collect on our Website. By accessing any external sites, you are agreeing to the privacy policies of those sites. Please understand that the external sites may have different policies with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information. We have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. Therefore, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of all third party websites. Without limiting anything in the following section, we are not liable in any way for the actions, inactions or policies of any external website.

 **Children**

The Website is not intended for the use of children. We do not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 and hereby specifically prohibit any user under the age of 13 from providing us with any Personal Information. If you are a parent of child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at [customercare@tadashishoji.com](mailto:%20customercare@tadashishoji.com) and we will delete the information from our system

If you are between the age of 13 and 18, please obtain your parents’ permission prior to registering with our Website or providing us with any Personal Information.

 **Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the “Privacy” section of our Website with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Privacy Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the Website or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice.

 **Website Security**

It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the Personal Information we collect online. We take reasonable precautions to protect our customers' Personal Information against loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We use encryption technology whenever receiving and transferring your Personal Information on our site. When you place an order or access your Personal Information on this Web site, we offer the use of a secure server. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk.. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by email and you do so at your own risk.

If for any reason you cannot access our secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the “Order Now” phone number listed on each website.

When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information or credit card information we take reasonable steps to require that they comply with this Privacy Policy and otherwise protect your Personal Information (including any credit card information).

If there is a breach of security involving your credit card information from our Website, we will inform you immediately and take commercially reasonable steps to rectify such breach.

If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third party, please immediately notify us via e-mail at: [customercare@tadashishoji.com](mailto:%20customercare@tadashishoji.com).

In the event you choose to establish an account with us, you should not share your login information with anyone.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

This Website operates AS-IS, and we do not represent or warrant that the Website will be available at all times, or that your use of the Website will be uninterrupted or error-free. We are not responsible for your ability to access this Website, or for matters beyond our control. This Privacy Policy is governed by California law, excluding its provisions on choice of law. This Website is intended for the use of US entities and individuals and runs on US-based servers, and we make no attempt to comply with the privacy (or security) policies of any country other than the United States. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information, but cannot assure that it will not be inadvertently disclosed.

If you have any general questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [customercare@tadashishoji.com](mailto:%20customercare@tadashishoji.com).
